CHRIS NASTRO

<u>cnastro@cloud.com</u> 347.728.1778 inkedin.com/in/chrisnastro/

Manager • Coordinator

Plan • Analyze • Manage • Execute

Enthusiastic, efficient, hardworking and experienced individual with a versatile skill set. An innovative problem solver with a passion for teamwork complimented by several years of experience in sales, event planning, and media interaction performing and managing across all levels.

Earned reputation for providing keen insights to partners and skillfully navigating competing business priorities. Couples' product knowledge with an in depth understanding of business requirements to ensure desired outcomes are achieved. Proven & experienced Manager with the values team building, trust, collaboration, and communication as a foundation to a successful career.

AREAS OF EXPERTISE

- Product Strategy & Distribution Planning
- Business Analysis
- Market Analysis/Marketing
- Client/Customer Experience
- Database Management

- Service Delivery
- Management/Change Management
- Sales Experience
- Promotional Marketing
- Account Management

PROFESSIONAL EXPERIENCE

ARTISANAL BREWING VENTURES, Brooklyn, NY

2021 - Current

Market Manager

- Provide management, oversight, and support for over five hundred on and off premise accounts
- Analyzes, plans, and executes sales promotions; ensures intake of seasonal and specialty items at mandated retail accounts
- Partners and works closely with Field Marketing and Brand Marketing to ensure execution of highvolume promotional events and ad campaigns
- Identifies and analyzes market trends to assist in determining future product opportunities and subsequent marketing campaigns
- Analyzes, plans, coordinates, and implements rollout strategies for new product markets

MANHATTAN BEER DISTRIBUTORS. Brooklyn, NY

2017 - 2019

Sales Representative

- Served over 150 on and off premise accounts; took orders, managed A/R, and provided accounts with the tools they required to help them succeed
- Collaborated closely with supplier representatives to set up and execute promotions at various accounts
- Utilized a product portfolio with thousands of SKUs (which included beer, wine, liquor, energy drinks, and water) to find the right fit for each account to ensure maximum profitability for the company and clients

CHRIS NASTRO linkedin.com/in/chrisnastro PAGE 2 OF 2

NATIONAL HOCKEY LEAGUE, New York, NY

2011 - 2017

Player Safety Coordinator

- Monitored, logged, and analyzed NHL games on a nightly basis to determine any potential supplemental discipline
- Led project to implement and maintain both the NHL Player Safety Video Database and the Supplemental Discipline Database
- Assisted in writing script and editing video of Supplemental Discipline decisions for release to media channels and public
- Assembled department specific presentations for NHL Board of Governors meetings, NHL General Manager meetings, NHL Rookie Orientation Programs, & Supplemental Discipline hearings
- Department of Player Safety Twitter account ensuring relevant news is released from the league timely and accurately

CEBU BAR & BISTRO, Brooklyn, NY

2006 - 2011

Front of House Manager, Bartender, Server

- Maintained stock of liquor and dry goods; made final purchasing decisions on necessary equipment and restaurant maintenance
- Completed scheduling management of up to forty employees
- Oversaw all advertising, promotions, and event planning

RED BULL ENERGY DRINK, Brooklyn, NY

2004 - 2006

Marketing Analyst/Event Planner

- Collaborated with executives, government officials, and high profile "extreme" athletes to plan events in the Greater New York City area (e.g., Red Bull Music Academy)
- Educated consumers on product lineup at events, colleges, and trade shows

SKYLINE LEGAL TECHNOLOGIES, New York, NY

2004 - 2006

IT Technician

- Analyzed, set up and maintained physical computer network for entire organization and made final purchasing decision on technology products
- Created and managed highly confidential documents

SKILLS

Proficient in Microsoft Office, Adobe Photoshop, iDig VIP, and all social media platforms

EDUCATION

Currently enrolled in Rutgers Full Stack Coding Program; expected completion date of April 2024

REFERENCES

Available upon request